[Disclaimer: Characters, locations,
and all depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
With the engagement plummeting like this,
would any client
in their right mind still pick us?
Can't you just play along?
Maybe it's because
I had to do it with you...
That's why I don't feel like it.
I'm sorry.
We're gonna be in trouble
if someone sees this.
This isn't gonna get us in trouble.
But this is.
Let go!
What the heck are you doing?
Something you despise doing with me,
yet you seem so comfortable
with someone else.
I'm cramping!
Help!
Ow!
Whoa, Wan!
Ow, I'm cramping!
[Episode 4: "First Punch"]
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
♫I wanna let the world know,
you wanna close it♫
♫Just wanna tell you, I'm doing fine, fine♫
♫You won't reveal it, but I won't conceal it♫
♫Trust me, it's alright♫
♫You do you♫
♫You can love whoever♫
♫But I like you forever♫
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
♫No pressure, no drama♫
♫Hakuna Matata♫
♫Just somebody who likes ya♫
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
♫No pressure, no drama♫
♫Hakuna Matata♫
♫Just somebody who likes ya♫
♫I'm just a fanboy♫
[Mr. Fanboy Series]
Thank you, Coach.
Are you okay?
I'm okay...
Wan...
Thanks for saving me,
and...
I'm sorry I almost drowned you.
It's alright, Nine.
And are you alright?
What's the matter?
Why are you here?
For the workshop, of course.
You finally made it.
What's your role?
I read the pilot script.
You're not in it.
Are you an extra?
I'm playing as your daddy.
Why did you drag me out here?
Worried about me?
Want me to say it in front of everyone?
That way, they will see your true colors.
So you really are worried.
Not about you.
About Wan?
Right...
Because he likes me,
you're worried
he won't be able to handle it?
You've taken it too far this time.
That's someone's life.
What did I take too far?
I was cramping.
If you act like
such a piece of shit again,
I guarantee
we won't take it outside like this again.
I'll say it right then and there,
loud and clear,
what a piece of shit you are.
How scary.
That totally wowed me.
Hey, where are you going?
Massage my feet first...
Partner.
Why are you picking me up, Mama?
Isn't this your day off?
Enlighten me.
When you were cramping,
was it real, or were you faking it?
It was real.
Listen.
What you did
was just like those characters
in old primetime soap operas
they keep rerunning.
Did you actually see it?
Why do you see me in such a bad light?
Nine,
you can fool
anyone in this world,
but it won't be me.
I can see through you.
Even Third caught on.
If you're gonna act all cute and innocent,
do it with someone else, not me.
Don't fucking get mad at me.
If something happens to you,
it's not gonna end there.
Things could get out of hand.
And if there were security cameras,
what were you planning to do?
They won't check the footage
if the actors are in a workshop, Mama.
I know that!
What I meant was, what are you gonna do
if it gets leaked?
Sorry, Mama...
I just snapped.
You...
always do shit without talking to me.
Next time, give me a heads-up.
I'll always be on your side.
What are you afraid of?
Got it?
[Reading the script]
[All day, every day]
The iPad is for working on the script.
The perfume
is for filming a review for Cher.
Mm, smells good.
Let me just
put it right there, dear client.
I almost drowned earlier.
I'll take it for you in a bit.
Ugh...
No!
Revenge must be taken.
Gratitude must be repaid.
What kind of saying was that?
What am I on about?
Just make a quick thank-you call
and get it over with,
or else I'm gonna go insane.
Hello.
What?
Thank you.
For what?
For helping me today.
So?
I'm saying thank you!
What more do you want?
Do you want me to bow at your feet?
What's the matter with you?
I have manners, that's what!
I know how to behave
when someone gives me a hand.
I'm hanging up!
Wait.
Are you an AI?
You only know a few words.
Let me put your IQ to the test.
Do you actually believe
that Nine was really cramping?
Well, he was cramping.
He really was!
Hey, I already told you
not to be so pessimistic.
Okay,
so your IQ is below 70.
Thanks. I got 70.
That just proved it.
Ugh!
Third!
Mr. Stud with an IQ of 180!
Einstein himself, aren't you?!
I'm gonna block you!
Unbelievable.
You have low EQ, too.
Stop talking about...
EQ and IQ already, you dumbass!
Huh?
What did you just say?
You dumbass! Dumbass! Dumbass!
Dumbass! Dumbass! Dumbass!
You dumbass! You dumbass!
You dumbass!!
Ugh!
[Call ended]
Damn it!
Shouldn't have called that jerk!
Shut up! Bastard!
I can't focus on my homework!
I'm sorry!
That was from next door.
Next door, my ass!
[Shooting Day]
[The Deep Between Us Q1]
Oh.
Hello, Cher.
Hello, Nine.
Hi, Wan.
Nine, are you waiting for Sunny?
Wanna walk to the dressing room with us?
Oh...
- So, like...
- He's good.
We're on a different floor.
A lead actor
and "the other actor"
aren't on the same level.
Let's go, sweetie.
We have a VIP room.
A sky loft, that is.
They have a sky loft as a makeup room?
Don't get confused.
That's showbiz for you.
Start learning today.
We should go, too. Come on.
Alright.
Sky,
I need to talk to you.
So now you wanna talk?
You can do whatever.
I'm only asking you one thing.
Leave Noel alone.
Noel... That old...
Noel, that new boy of yours?
I'm sorry, Pai.
Cut!
Wan, it's been so many takes,
and none of them work!
Luang, you're the acting coach.
Go help him get it right.
What you've learned about chakra opening,
put it to use.
Tell the scriptwriter to write
lines that come naturally to him.
Hold up...
The actor can't act,
and you're seriously
blaming the scriptwriter?
How are they supposed to do that?
Give the script legs
and have it run out of his mouth?!
Yeah, aren't we supposed to be a team?!
Huh?
And the actor needs to learn
to fend for himself!
You asked if I could help him act?
Sure, I can.
But his brain and his memory can't!
Cannot, okay?
- Let's take a break, then!
- Haven't I told you
to recast him from the start?
Taking a break!
Fine, do that!
After this, he needs to pull this off!
And the person who'll make that happen
is the acting coach.
I'm not fucking doing that!
Do it yourself if you're so good!
Bitch...
Why the fuck did we hire an acting coach?!
Alright, guys...
Let's take a break.
Come on, go take a break.
Hurry, go take your break.
Be back at 11:30.
Quick, chop-chop!
Damn it, go!
Boy, go memorize your lines!
Come on.
The stuff I have to deal with each day.
As if that boy can act. Did you see it?
15 takes, are you nuts?
Ugh!
Let's gulp down 10 coffees.
Mama,
I'd like a latte, no sweet, oat milk,
and make it a double shot.
And one orange juice, Mom.
Thank you, Kateyki.
This morning's coffee didn't
even get to say hi to my stomach.
Anyone can tell he can't act.
How did he get past the casting team?
There's always one troublemaker on set.
Get the pic?
Except for you and me, though.
Not us.
Walls have ears, y'all.
Exactly.
So be careful when you gossip, yeah?
Mm...
So which of you
are the "walls" and the "ears"?
It's screaming, "Busybodies!"
You damn twosome
should use this time to practice
holding those hairdryers and brushes properly.
Your skills...
are mid.
- A trashy bunch.
- True.
Fake bitches!
Whoa!
What did you say?!
I call you guys "Queens."
What did you hear?
Queens?
Yep.
You just called us "fake bitches."
Well, that'd be correct.
So your ears still work fine!
Oh...
That nasty mouth. Wanna fight?!
No. It'll stain your hands.
Once your back doesn't have an ouchie,
schedule it then,
you old farts!
Your mom's the old fart!
We're close enough for you
to crack a "your mom" joke?
Bastard!
Asshole!
You bitch!
Bitch!
Bring it on!
- Come on!
You start, then!
Stop!
I already have enough headaches as it is!
I'm gonna fire all you HMUAs!
How does that sound?!
We're running lines
in case it gives you
some ideas for the dialogue.
Cliché, isn't it?
Just like when the HMUAs on set fight, Pai.
Stuff your faces
with food or drinks, would you?
That way, no one talks.
Pai!
Let me just say one thing...
Kick these bitches
out of our lives.
Keep them miles away from us.
Or else
you're gonna have
a problem with ThirdNine.
- Ugh...
- Also,
just so you know,
I have other work besides this gig.
I get paid a lot more
for event gigs.
Then go ahead and take those.
We'll take it all from here.
Have some manners, bastard.
I haven't even finished.
I said, "Stop," so can you just
go your separate ways?!
You two, go that way.
Eat your omakase.
Satisfied?
Yes!
Yeah.
Mama, whip up
some omakase for them.
Sure thing.
You two, go eat noodle soup.
- Yes.
Over there. Do you eat noodle soup?
Yes.
Eat those sushi pieces with
the Angry Birds fish-ball topping!
Come on, let's eat.
- True.
- Soon, they're not gonna be so free.
Right on.
♫It's probably time to put them down,♫
♫My feelings that hound♫
Don't even know what that damn song is.
- Why?
- Haven't heard of it.
Never? It's a song of taste!
Bitch, I bet the singer's already dead.
Dead, my fucking ass!
Are you the singer?
No, I just like to protect everyone.
- Right.
- Love the world.
Come on, try saying it again, Wan.
So now you wanna talk?
Noel, is he your new special someone?
Interesting.
You did it.
So which part are you stuck on?
Do you want Luang's help?
Struggling with the first scene, Wan?
That's right, Nine.
Honestly, you would've had to...
really do your homework.
I don't know how I can help,
apart from...
wishing you luck.
Right.
Try pulling yourself together.
You might just waste
less of everyone's time on set.
Thank you, Nine.
I'll try not to be a dead weight.
Hey...
you're a smart one.
You catch on fast.
Nice technique.
Complex, but effective.
Mm...
Nine, let's go eat.
Third, are you coming?
No.
Tell me if you need anything.
Nine, let's go.
Cher,
I'll take it from here.
There's nothing else to lose.
I'll leave it to you, Third.
What, Cher?
Come on.
Just go.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
He's just being a poser,
but he can definitely help.
Go get his help.
Go.
Go. Follow him.
There.
That's Nine's chair.
It's fine. Take a seat.
The first day is always like this.
No pressure.
Just focus.
Shut everything else off for now
and just focus on your part.
Now, how do you see this scene?
What are they doing?
Copter wants Sky
to stop messing with Noel,
but Sky won't listen.
And why does he do all that?
He wants revenge.
He wants...
Copter to be in as much pain as he is.
You do understand the scene.
What's the reason you can't act?
Have you figured it out?
I think...
maybe it's the nerves and the pressure.
If you feel pressured
or nervous,
focus only on the person
you're acting with.
How do I do that?
There are so many people.
I can't just ignore them, can I?
What you do is...
only look at me.
Only listen to me.
Stay with me.
If you could do all that,
I'd be the only one you'd see.
Give it a try.
I'm ready.
Sky.
I need to talk to you.
Only look at me.
Only listen to me.
Stay with me.
Take it easy.
Pick it up whenever you're ready.
So now you wanna talk?
Only look at me.
Stay with me.
You can do whatever.
I'm only asking you one thing.
Leave Noel alone.
Noel, is he your new special someone?
Interesting.
Mm,
now you're with your scene partner.
You're not, though.
How do you know?
It's pretty obvious.
♫You keep your eyes on me♫
♫Keep your eyes on me♫
I'm sorry, Nine.
Hey, it's alright.
You can sit.
I'm chill.
I'm going to see Cher.
Excuse me.
What an intense course.
Stop meddling.
I can, though.
We're partners, after all.
If my man messes around
with someone else...
as his hubby,
I've gotta get him back, right?
Consider yourself lucky
I'd even work with you.
You like Wan?
Mm...
I do.
He seems natural
and knows how to behave in the industry.
If we're partners,
it might work out just great.
Just like you and me
back in high school, huh?
Don't you just miss the old days
back when I was stupid?
You're not getting any smarter, though.
Hey...
wait up!
Partner.
Sky,
I need to talk to you.
So now you wanna talk?
You can do whatever you want to me.
I'm only asking you one thing.
Leave Noel alone.
Noel, that new special someone of yours?
Interesting.
Don't say I didn't warn you.
Leave Noel alone.
Cut...
That was good.
Let's continue to the next one.
Wan, that was amazing.
What a miracle!
What miracle?
He just happened
to recall lessons I've taught.
Oh...
Get the idea?
You need me.
Fine, fine, fine.
Here, let's link pinkies to make up.
That's a wrap!
Thank you, cast and crew!
See you again in the next cue.
Don't be late!
Nine!
You're taking the same ride as me, right?
I don't think so.
Wan!
I want to invite you for a meal.
You wanna... invite me?
Yes.
Are you coming?
Maybe not today, Nine.
I want Wan to get some rest today.
I only ate a little this evening.
Apart from that...
I noticed you never had time to eat
because you were so busy rehearsing.
Please?
Right,
when I approached you
with all that tension,
it was actually because of Third.
I'm...
having some problems with him.
It's just that...
he said I drowned you intentionally.
Let me put your IQ to the test.
Do you actually believe
that Nine was really cramping?
Well, he was cramping.
I'm just worried that you'd get me wrong.
I really was cramping.
Right.
But that's just how Third is.
He's always pessimistic
and...
like, he makes false accusations
to make someone look like the bad guy.
But I do believe
that you'd definitely understand me
because you've been in my shoes before.
At first,
Third also made you out to be the bad guy,
but I guess...
it's my turn now?
So I'm just confused,
wondering if it's because...
Third wants to part ways.
Uh... Mama.
- Hm?
- I forgot my phone.
But as I see it...
it's like he already wants to part ways.
He's probably got his eye on you.
I don't think so, Nine.
I could never compare to you.
I think Third...
has the best partner in the world.
Mm...
He's so lucky to have you as his partner.
Then...
can I ask you a straight question?
What are your feelings toward Third
right now?
Is it still the same?
So that means
what he's doing to you is working.
Because today,
Third told me that he liked you,
that you seemed natural,
and that it'd work out great
if you guys were partners.
See?
That means Third
is trying to drive a wedge
between you and me.
How about this?
If you don't want us to fight,
try to keep your distance from him.
The reason I'm having
this conversation with you today,
warning you,
is that...
I'm sure...
you wouldn't lie,
betray me,
or hurt me.
Rest assured.
I'll do everything I can
to help you succeed, Nine,
because I'm your fanboy.
Thanks,
my No. 1 fanboy.
So what do you think?
I think I believe him.
I only got to know Third recently, too.
Helping or coaching me
doesn't mean
he's actually nice to me, yeah?
Hey... think it through.
You just got to know Nine, too, didn't you?
Like...
getting to know him
as an actor you like and as a coworker
are two different things.
Are you taking your fave's side?
Ugh!
And you're not?
You put him on a pedestal,
praising him like he's some deity.
Hey,
Wan.
I really think you need to slow down
and use your brain.
I know you're not that dumb.
Why are you digressing?
Just say you're taking Third's side.
I'm not taking his side!
But I genuinely believe
Third's a good person.
I don't know if I can believe that.
Lately, Third's been
coming around me differently, too.
Him coming around you
doesn't mean
he's gonna hurt Nine or you, right?
If Nine and Third
don't like each other's guts,
then it's their business, isn't it?
Let's say you were close to Third,
and they're really on bad terms.
It doesn't mean you have to
take anyone's side, right?
I don't know.
You...
have to observe and see how it goes.
Anyone can say
whatever they want, no?
Everybody wants
to look good in the eyes of others.
You,
just be sweet.
Don't judge him
based on other people's words.
Sure!
Yes, Mom!
It's okay to be careful,
but don't be paranoid.
That's gonna wreck you,
I'll tell you that.
Now, go to sleep.
Aren't you on location tomorrow?
Mm.
Go sleep properly!
Catch!
[Shooting Day]
[The Deep Between Us Q2]
Oh?
You're always early.
Good. How consistent of you.
But I've taught you before, right?
Didn't I teach you
the Exclusive Star 102 course?
Tell me, when you become famous,
what will you do, sweetie?
You have to be late
so that the other cast and crew
move mountains for you.
I'm using the 101 course.
I spent the night here.
You're kidding!
Someone like you spending the night?
Not buying it!
I'm gonna go.
See you. I'm gonna go have a meal.
Yeah, run along.
Run along. Has Pai arrived?
Wow, that boy. He ignored me.
- If I arrive after him, I'll get yelled at!
- He has this side to him?
- Hello, Jern.
- Oh?
Hi there.
- Uh...
- You're here early.
Right...
Uh...
You and Third are close?
Not really.
Sike!
We're close. Why?
Uh...
I just wanna know.
What kind of person is he?
He's nice,
but boy, is he blunt.
Whatever he thinks, he speaks.
Sometimes...
he even chews people out.
You know that, sweetie!
Actually, I don't like
gossiping or anything,
but there's more to spill!
Third is punctual.
He's easy to work with,
except for one thing, sweetie.
He likes asking,
asking,
and asking!
So much so that he goes on and on
and on and on and on and on.
But that's good...
By the time
he comes on set, he's good to go.
Isn't that right, sweetie?
- It is.
- Meanwhile, some actors...
don't even memorize their lines,
and when they're on set,
I don't even know if they're gonna act.
They just snap, snap,
snap, snap, snap,
and snap nonstop!
How about I chop it off
if you're not doing your job?
Not even memorizing the script.
The reason I was hired
is to run the set,
not the other ten fucking things!
Am I doing the work of a kraken?
Ten shits just to get paid for one.
You're... catching stray bullets?
Wow, a whole cartridge.
No...
I'm just speaking generally.
- Oh... okay.
- Just in general.
In general!
Totally general.
Sweetie,
ask away if you don't get it.
- Alright.
- Ask a bunch.
A bunch.
Okay.
ThirdNine, are you ready?
Okay, come on.
Team, are we ready?
Alright, let's go.
Ready for a detailed shot? Come on.
Alright, kids. Watch.
Watch and learn how it's done.
One day, you'll have to act like they do.
Not today, though.
Capisce?
Jern.
All set? What are we waiting for?
Ugh, I'm calling it!
And...
action!
You're worried about something, right?
Mm...
Don't focus on anything else.
Just focus on swimming.
Well, that's all I want to focus on,
but...
I'm also
worried about you.
Cut!
Fabulous!
Nine, Third, come to me at the monitor.
Yeah, come on. I don't wanna move.
- It's hot. Come on.
- It's good. I like it.
This take feels relaxing.
Yeah, I think
the variations in eye contact
are a lot better than in the workshop.
- That's a print.
- I think...
'Cause I'm about to bail.
So the next one is an action scene,
which isn't my job.
I'm heading out
because I've got an event after, okay?
- I'm leaving. Bye, y'all!
- Goodbye.
- Thank you very much.
- A bad example. Taking on overlapping jobs.
- What? Who takes on overlapping jobs?
- You shouldn't be doing that.
I took on that job before this one.
You're the one overlapping.
Can I ask you a straight question?
What are your feelings toward Third?
Are they still the same?
Send in the guards, please.
There's a stalking sasaeng in here.
Keep your focus here.
Think of it as a flower.
One...
Two...
Three...
Only look at me.
Only listen to me.
Stay with me.
How about this?
If you don't want us to fight,
Try to keep a distance from him.
I'm sure...
you wouldn't lie
or hurt me.
Rest assured.
I'll do everything I can
to help you succeed, Nine,
because I'm your fanboy.
Alrighty, come on. Let's get to filming.
Then, for those two,
I'll have them stand over there.
- Mm.
- Like a couple of twinkles.
Alright? They won't
block the punch that way.
Sure. Move the mark so that it...
Sure, sure, sure.
Where am I standing, Jern?
Come on, come on.
Main characters like you boys,
stand right here. You're gonna be stars.
There, there, there.
You'll feel like a twinkle, sweeties.
Just at first.
Once you become famous, bam,
you're gonna shine brighter, like stars.
Alright.
You two, get the marks right.
Pai will come in for the blocking.
- Pai, go ahead.
- I'm gonna go ahead with the briefing.
Alright, action scenes
are my strong suit.
It's easy-peasy.
- Right.
- You two...
stand right on the marks.
And when you punch,
just swing past him like so, bam.
Yeah, and you just flick
in the same direction.
Give it a try.
Swing past him, bam.
Yeah.
And whether you wanna flick,
fall to the ground, or stay standing,
- it's up to you. Go with the flow. Got it?
- Why are you staring at me?
- Look over there!
- And don't pull any method acting on me.
This scene, yeah?
- Right.
- Use your imagination.
- Swinging past his face looks realistic.
- Sure thing.
I say it's easy.
Let's get to filming.
Alright. Come on, kids.
Be on standby, sweeties.
Get the slate ready.
Just a sec.
Right, crew members, keep silent.
Ready, go.
Roll... camera!
- Camera rolling, sound rolling.
- Camera speed!
Scene 4, Cut 1, Take 1.
Set!
Alright, set.
And...
action!
Is this...
the promising young shark
Coach praises so much?
All I can see is a fucking loser.
Shut up!
Can't handle some sting?
Why are you staring at me?
Angry?
Are you angry?
Or you can't handle the truth I said?
You hate me
because you were
gonna break up with Bas and fall for me?
You!
Ow!
- Whoa!
- Third!
Cut!
Jern, go check on Third!
Was that a real hit?
Third,
did that split your lip?
Let me see.
Wan!
Does it hurt?
You hit him for real?
What went wrong in that briefing?
There aren't any safeguards for him?
That was intentional, wasn't it?
Sunny...
I...
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
What a shitty thing to say!
Just because you said you didn't mean it,
you think it's over?
Well, he said he didn't mean to.
It was an accident.
Fine.
Then, all of you here,
how are you gonna pay
for Third getting hurt?
I saw you rehearse that briefing for ages.
Why did you still mess up?
What happened to Third
was a serious hit, Pai.
VE ENT can sue you all.
I'll sue you all.
Ms. Sunny, how about...
I...
First of all, I apologize on his behalf.
It was an accident.
Please don't take it to court.
I think we can settle this.
Sure.
Go on. I'm listening.
Sunny,
no one is being sued.
That's not possible, Third.
Does it hurt?
I'm okay.
Then, we're taking a break.
He needs to rest.
Uh...
But... But Miss,
we're already going over schedule.
I don't care.
If you're smart enough, figure it out.
Come on.
Jern, you idiot!
You really asked her that!
Why the hell did you?!
Just to get roasted?!
I'm the director,
but you didn't even help.
What kind of assistant are you?
You assist in making it worse.
Let's just use...
the take with the real hit.
That works. So realistic.
You, shoot some B-roll footage and wrap up.
Cher...
I wanna check on Third!
Not now.
But I want to apologize to him.
Not right now, Wan.
Right now, everyone is raging.
If you go, you'll only lose.
This is gonna be a big deal.
We have to talk to Wut
and fix it afterwards.
But I really didn't mean to, Cher.
They don't care
whether you meant to or not.
They're gonna use
this whole thing to crush you.
Pitch,
can we file a lawsuit?
What can we do?
Should we talk to the legal department?
What are we gonna get out of this
if we take this further?
Something's gotta be done, Pitch.
Our actor was punched.
Or...
should we leak the vid?
That'll screw everyone equally.
Stop this stupidity.
If it goes south, it goes south.
But if all goes well,
that Wan kid will get even more clout.
They're definitely
taking this matter to North.
I will take this matter to North.
Now, we can finally...
squeeze that brat out.
Should we beat them to it
with a statement?
Say it's an accident.
That's worse than just being defensive.
I believe North already knows.
It now comes down
to what he's gonna do to us.
But right now...
we have to contain
this matter from leaking outside,
or else it'll be even harder to fix.
[Cher, the video of me
punching Third is all over X]
It's too late, Wut.
Wan!
You hit him for real?
What went wrong in that briefing?
- There aren't any safeguards for him?
- We're doomed...
Jern, go check on Third!
Did that split your lip?
You did this?
Well, where did you get the video?
I have eyes and ears on set.
Any move that creates buzz
is good for the series.
No harm to you, since
you have nothing to do with this.
If there's drama,
there's fame.
Uh...
I mean...
what if it creates more buzz for Wan?
Well...
Lucky for him, I guess?
[#DivingDeeperIntoTheSet]
[I knew it; rushing down
to help a fan was for clout]
[He punched my baby boy? I'm cursing him!]
[Cher]
Hello, Cher?
Keep still, Wan.
The company will sort this out.
How am I supposed to keep still, Cher?
Just do.
Have faith in us.
You, stop scrolling
and go to bed.
Alright.
[third.tharit]
[wan_ashawin]
Hello, you...
What?
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to.
Honestly, I'm not calling to make excuses.
It's just...
I miscalculated the reach.
I didn't think it would hit you.
"Rewarded good with evil."
I helped someone but got injured?
I'm sorry.
Chew me out however you want.
I yield!
So you want me to chew you out
because that punch
was actually intentional?
No... you.
Are you crazy?
Why would I punch you on purpose?
So why do you want me to chew you out?
Well...
I'm being chewed out so badly
that I'm trending.
But well...I deserved it.
I hurt someone's fave.
Don't you think it's strange?
Grumbling to the person you punched?
It is.
Honestly...
I feel so bad
because you're an actor.
You make a living with your face.
I'm so...
Don't mind it.
Huh?
I meant, you need to take responsibility.
If you can do that, I'll forgive you.
How do I take responsibility?
[The footage was part
of a crucial scene in the pilot shoot
and was only a rehearsal filmed
under the close supervision of the staff;
as the producer, we apologize
if the unauthorized disclosure of the video
caused any discomfort
or misunderstanding regarding the actor]
[NPY]
That little statement was not okay.
Even though it was an accident,
Third was genuinely hurt.
This is damaging to me.
From the start, I told you to fire Wan.
I believe you have something to consider.
I'm considering not letting
Nine and Third continue with this project.
Is it really that big of a deal?
You asked if we could remove the boy?
I stand by what I said.
I can find him a new project.
Honestly, though,
throwing the million baht you spent
on the pilot down the drain,
are you seriously doing that?
It's just a million-ish.
I can cover it.
If money isn't a problem,
you need to clear Wan's name,
because if he quits right now,
people will think Wan's in the wrong.
Well, he is!
What fucking names
do you want me to clear?!
I don't think
Wan's that much in the wrong.
No? Are you sure about that?
Assault isn't wrong?
How about this?
Just put it out there
that Wan miscued and punched Third.
I'm dying to know
what netizens think.
So now, the production team
is at fault, isn't it?
This was careless filming.
An action scene
needs an action director,
even if it's only one scene.
That means...
you're at fault, right, North?
What a clown.
You realize you're reaching
so fucking far that you don't make sense?!
I'm only stating the facts,
unlike you,
who always tries to get the kid fired.
I've seen what Wan did wrong
twice now.
I insist that if you remove Wan,
the company has to release
a statement dismissing him
and acknowledge the mistake
on the production team's part.
But if you can't do that...
I'll take this to court
and state that
the production team was at fault
for not taking good care of my actor.
That's enough.
Enough...
Aren't we in this as business partners?
How long is this going to go on?
Like...
if there's drama,
isn't that free publicity, guys?
A win for me,
for you,
and for you.
Yeah!
So shouldn't we
solve the problem at its root?
Guys, how about this?
I think...
we should generate buzz
about the male lead and the antagonist
not being close at all in real life.
Think about it.
How invested would the viewers be?
Huh, silence.
Alright, I'll help you settle this.
I already have a promotional project planned.
I will bring the boys
together.
No.
I don't mind.
Pitch, Pitch.
Think long-term.
Look ahead.
The reason for bringing them together
is that I'll make
ThirdNine trend through candid moments.
We're gonna make it so real
that people see how loving these two are,
which is...
something that...
you can't achieve right now.
Am I right?
Isn't this a win-win?
But I do have one condition.
There will be no entourage.
I don't think this is appropriate.
No,
I think there's gotta be an entourage.
No, guys...
That wasn't a question.
Thank you.
Hello.
Uh, I...
have a delivery for Room 3006.
Please allow me a moment
to contact the resident.
Sure.
Hello,
there's a delivery for you.
The resident said you could go upstairs.
Alright.
The elevator is right there.
Ok, right...
Thank you.
I'm here to take responsibility.
ICHITAN Iced Tea Lemon Cold Brew Style.
I just did a review of this.
Here.
Have you had it?
Huh?
You brought that for me
cause I told you to take responsibility?
Mm.
What did you expect?
ICHITAN is the best!
They're sponsoring the series, too.
Drink a whole lot.
We might end up as brand ambassadors!
What?!
Why didn't you take it?
Shut the door!
Wow...
I didn't chew you out,
but the fans did.
How are you feeling?
It hurts...
Those keyboard warriors
would say anything.
Don't dwell on it.
I'm trying not to read it.
But you've been a Nine fan.
I suppose you badmouthed me,
didn't you?
Sometimes.
Sometimes
would mean oftentimes.
Right,
why were you avoiding me that day?
On set, I meant.
What?
Who did?
No one.
Before you punched me,
all you did was avoid me.
Before I knew it...
we were growing intimate.
You're still babbling.
How about I get intimate again?!
How so?
Like this?
Punches hurt.
Next time, I'll only allow cheeks.
Did that one punch
mess you up in the head?
How about you get it checked?
Just cut to the chase.
Why were you avoiding me?
And don't you lie.
Well, you...
were being so nice to me
just to mess with me.
Why would I do that?
Well...
Nine...
Were you being gaslit?
And you still believed that?
Don't say anything bad about Nine.
I wasn't gaslit or anything at all.
I was just observing
if that was true.
So was it?
I don't know.
Still deciding.
Then, I'll give you as much time as you need
because you...
are stuck with me for a long time.
♫Just a gentle, gentle gaze♫
♫Only a gentle gaze, left or right♫
♫If we meet eyes for a while,♫
♫Wouldn't it be
too irresistible to try?♫
♫Just a gentle, gentle gaze♫
♫On me♫
♫You keep your eyes on me♫
♫On me, on me♫
♫Wouldn't it be dangerous
if we fall deeply?♫
We're gonna have the cast members
do some activities together.
Go follow someone else!
Nah!
Following you is the most fun.
"See his eyes
when he's talking about Wan?
Why don't you change
your partner already, you bastard?!"
Right now, do you like me
or Third more?
You can like or love him,
but you have to love yourself, too.
How?
In a series...
the two male leads
have gotta kiss now, right?
♫If you're not into me,♫
♫Stop playing already♫
♫Before my heart loses its cool♫
♫Left or right, what should we do?♫
♫Alright,♫
♫I'm only looking at you,♫
♫But if you're not on the same frequency,♫
♫Please don't keep your eyes on me♫
♫On me, on me♫
♫Keep your eyes on me♫
♫I could really fall in love, you crazy♫
♫You said to only look at you♫
♫Alright, now there's only you in my sight♫
♫You said to only listen to you♫
♫Uh-huh, now there's only
your voice in my mind♫
♫How your eyes smile when you gleam♫
♫The sound of your voice feels like a dream♫
♫"Look at me,♫
♫Listen to me"♫
♫You said it all, what does it mean?♫
♫If you're not into me,♫
♫Stop playing already♫
♫Before my heart loses its cool♫
♫Left or right, what should we do?♫
♫Alright,♫
♫I'm only looking at you,♫
♫But if you're not on the same frequency,♫
♫Please don't keep your eyes on me♫
♫Just a gentle, gentle gaze♫
♫Keep your eyes on me♫
♫Only a gentle gaze, left or right♫
♫If we meet eyes for a while♫
♫Keep your eyes on me♫
♫Wouldn't it be dangerous
if we fall deeply?♫
[Mr. Fanboy Series]